Contact

fulle024@cougars.csusm.edu

www.linkedin.com/in/brittany-f-5278728b (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Patient Safety
BLS
PALS

Brittany Fullen

Registered Nurse, BSN, RN, PHN, CEN, MICN

La Mesa, California

Summary

I am an experienced registered nurse with 8 years of experience with the last 6 years dedicated to emergency and trauma nursing. I have developed skills of self-awareness, integrity, transparency, and consistency which have allowed me to become a leader on my unit. Over the last 3 years I have been developing my skills as an educator. I am an active American Heart Association instructor for the disciplines of BLS, ACLS and PALS. I am currently enrolled in a MSN program focused on nursing education.

Experience

Sharp HealthCare Registered Nurse September 2015 - Present (4 years 11 months) San Diego, California

Clinical nurse in the Emergency Department

Key Medical Resources
Instructor
January 2017 - Present (3 years 7 months)
Southern California

I am a certified AHA instructor in BLS, ACLS, and PALS as well as teach continuing education courses for nurses and nursing assistants in a variety of area.

Pioneers Memorial Healthcare District Registered Nurse April 2014 - September 2015 (1 year 6 months) Brawley, California

Emergency Room

Community Health Systems Registered Nurse July 2012 - March 2014 (1 year 9 months)

Education

Western Governors University

MSN, Nursing Education · (2020 - 2022)

California State University San Marcos Bachelor's of Nursing (2007 - 2012)